var questionBank = [
    {   
        question: "What belongs to you, but is used by others?",
        selection: ["your sweater", "your car", "your name", "your socks"],
        answer: "your name"
    },
    {   
        question: "How many sides has a circle?",
        selection: ["One", "Two", "None", "I don't know"],
        answer: "Two"
    },
    {   
        question: "What wont run long without winding?", 
        selection: ["A airplane", "A river", "propellers", "i don't know"],
        answer: "A river"
    },
    {
        question: "What has to be broken before you can use it",
        selection: ["A egg", "your socks", "a box", "nuts"],
        answer: "A egg"
    },
    {
        question: "What goes up and never goes down?",
        selection: ["your blood pressure", "superman", "taxes", "your age"],
        answer: "your age"
    },
    {
        question: "What has legs but cant walk?",
        selection: ["A cheetah", "A dog", "A chair", "a table"],
        answer: "a table"
    },
    {
        question: "People make me, save me, change me, and raise me. What am I?",
        selection: ["A baby", "A dog", "Money", "A painting"],
        answer: "Money"
    },
    {
        question: "What has hands but cannot clap?",
        selection: ["A clock", "A T-Rex", "A Monkey", "A baby"],
        answer: "A clock"
    },
    {
        question: "We're five little things of an everyday sort; you'll find us all in 'a tennis court' ",
        selection: ["tennis balls", "vowels", "rackets", "Serena Williams"],
        answer: "vowels"
    },
    {
        question: "What is always on its way here, but never arrives?",
        selection: ["A boat", "Amazon packages", "An airplane", "Tomorrow"],
        answer: "Tomorrow"
    },
    {
        question: "I get wet when drying. I get dirty when wiping. What am i?",
        selection: ["A car", "Kitchen table", "A towel", "I don't know"],
        answer: "A towel"
    }

];

